http://www.themoth.org/privacy-policy

Skip to Main Content
Privacy Policy
Last Updated: May 25, 2018The Moth (the “Company”) operates themoth.org (the “Site”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site. We use your Personal Information only for providing content and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in connection with this policy. If you are a European Union (EU) resident, please note that there are a number of provisions in this privacy policy that apply uniquely to you.Personal Information Collection and UseWhile using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name (“Personal Information”). The legal basis for processing your personal data is your consent.Log DataSimilar to many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, and other statistics. In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics, that collect, monitor and analyze this data. When you use a social media feature within the site, and you post to social media platforms, the social media site will provide us with some information about you.CommunicationsWe may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information which is voluntarily provided during the use of this Site. This includes information provided when signing up for our Newsletter, Donating to The Moth, entering contests, and when buying tickets for The Moth events.CookiesCookies are files with small amounts of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.SecurityYour personal data may be stored by third parties, via cloud services or other technology, to whom The Moth has contracted with, to support The Moth’s business operations. These third parties do not use or have access to your personal data other than for cloud storage and retrieval. The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Changes to Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy is effective as of May 25, 2018 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page. We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modification to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment and consent to abide by and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. Notice of any material changes to this Privacy Policy will be provided through the email address you have provided to us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.Your Choices & RightsWhere you have given us your consent, you can withdraw it by doing the following.
To stop receiving our marketing you can follow the unsubscribe instructions in any of the emails we send you or contact us and we will do it for you.To opt out of the use of cookies and tracking tools, please change the settings on your browser and/or device.To opt out of the use of tracking tools on third-party social media sites related to The Moth, please change the security settings on your account.You also have rights over how your personal information is used including:
The right to object to how we process your personal information.The right to request that your personal information be erased or restricted from further use.The right to request a copy of the information we hold about you.The right to correct, amend or update information you have given us
To exercise any of the above rights, and/or if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@themoth.org.
